Violin's You
I don't know.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Now, where the hell is he?
What is it you need?
What do you need? Lordeo!
Whole Horse, what is it you need?
I...
got a report.
A report?
That guy Polnareff, you see, he done
gone and defected to Joestar's outfit.
My dear whole horse,
the actions Polnareff chooses are
of very little consequence to me.
After all, errand boys are easy to
come by, wouldn't you say, whole horse?
You've wasted my time coming here.
And my time is very valuable.
Now run along, you still have work to do.
First and foremost, do hurry up with
the termination of the Joestars.
And this time, try not to disappoint me.
How dare you tell me to live
up to your expectations?
Just who do you think you are anyway?
Just look at you, sitting
there with your back to me?
Leaving yourself wide open!
Heh, everyone's just blowing
your rip out of proportion.
I never pledged eternal
loyalties to kiss my ass.
Adios, Dio.
You can regret this moment in hell.
What the?
Ah,
even at the moment of the kill,
your breathing is measured
and you perspire very little.
Not bad, whole horse.
Not bad at all.
What the hell?
How did he get behind me?
I...
I just don't get it.
I don't...
I just don't get it!
Why would I have a dream
like that right now?
If we continue at the rate at
which we're currently traveling,
we should make it to the Red
Sea in just a couple of days.
Here's where we are and once we pass
right through there we'll be in Egypt?
Every day we're getting closer!
Sorry to make you wait.
Let's go uh Mr Joestar who
is that you were talking to?
Oh that was just my friend in Egypt.
In any case, it's already been more
than 30 days since we left Japan.
There's no time to wait, so let's move on.
Ah, that's right.
Little lady, you're more beautiful
and breathtaking than a desert rose.
Whole horse.
Heck, I never imagined that you, yourself,
would be the one to come all the way
down here to meet with this old cowpoke.
Hey, hey, now don't you go
looking at me like that.
If you and I were to become partners,
well, hell, we'd be unbeatable.
Come on, let's look up.
You are so cold.
Hmm?
Shit!
What in the name of hell are you doing?
So, why do you suppose you were
asked to come here homeless?
Lord Dio has granted me this opportunity
to avenge the death of my son, J. Guile.
Avenge him?
How dare you abandon J.
Guile and shamelessly
make your way back here?
Hey now, just hold on there.
Listen, you got it all wrong.
By the time I arrived, J.
Guile was already dead.
Stop making excuses!
You shall atone for the
crime of abandoning J.
Guile by your death!
You too must have heard rumors,
but have never seen my stand.
Yes, let me show it to you, whole horse.
No, no way.
You're not going to...
My stand. Justice.
Justice?
What?
What's this? Mist?
Yes, a mist of death.
Death?
What the hell?
Hmm, a clean hole has opened now.
Yes, my stand, Justice,
is a stand of mist.
Whatever wound this mist touches
will end up with a hole like that.
Go dance with Justice.
Cut this shit off or I get mad.
Enough is enough.
You see, when the mist enters the
hole, it turns you into a puppet.
Die by your own stand, whole horse.
Justice prevails.
Polnareff, are you able to
see well enough to drive?
I've never seen such a
thick blanket of fog.
Yeah, it's getting pretty
hard to see the road up ahead.
That's odd.
It's only about three o 'clock.
We have no choice.
Let's stop in the next town and
look for a place to spend the night.
Sounds good.
Something strange about this town.
It's too quiet.
This place gives me the creeps.
Hey, Jotaro!
Oh, I guess you're right.
No point in just standing around.
Well then, let's go find a hotel.
Come on, doesn't anyone live in this town?
We can't even ask for directions.
Someone dumped a dead dog there.
That's disgusting!
What a smell!
Oh, there's someone now! Hey, mister!
Excuse me, but we're looking for a hotel.
Can we find a hotel with clean
bathrooms somewhere around here?
Really sorry to bother you while you're
napping, but could you wake up for a second?
Ah!
This guy is dead!
Why is he out on the street like this?
Could it be an accident or a heart attack?
It's possible.
But I don't think it's as simple
as some guy having a heart attack.
Why don't you pull his hand
out where we can see it?
Okay.
Whoa!
Oh!
The gun is still warm, which means not
much time has passed since it was fired.
So he shot himself then?
But where's the wound? Right here.
There's a hole underneath this guy's
throat the size of a ping-pong ball.
Is that the cause of death?
So where's the blood?
A wound like that should
have gushed blood like crazy,
leaving a big pool all around.
Normally, anyway.
Th-that's not all. Look at this.
I've never seen anything like it. Hm?
Wh-what happened to this dead body?
There are holes all over this man.
And not a trace of blood
from any of the wounds.
Why was he killed this way?
Is there some meaning to it?
Shit!
Someone tell me what the
hell is going on here!
Just calm down, Polar.
In any case, we have to get the police.
Madam, excuse me.
We need your help.
We need you to call the police.
There's a man lying dead in the street.
Excuse me. Hello.
Can't you hear me?
Are you talking to me?
What is it you want?
Oh, yes, there's a dead man
over there in the street.
We need you to call the
police as soon as possible.
Ah, a man.
I see.
So, you want me to
report it to the police?
Ah, so itchy.
If you would, madam.
We'd appreciate it if you'd hurry.
What's going on, anyway?
There seems to be something very wrong
with the people in this town, old man.
You know, I'm wondering if this could
be the work of another stand user.
What do you think?
Perhaps,
but I have no idea what our
pursuers would gain by murdering
an innocent man before we
even arrived in this town.
I just don't see the motive.
We shouldn't ignore the
possibility, though.
His death is just too damn weird.
Jostar-san, I have to agree with Jotaro.
If he's right and there's a stand user
hiding here, we are in serious danger.
And in that case, we need to
get out of here right away.
Are you suggesting we try
to escape in this fog?
Now that is what I call suicidal!
Then what are we supposed to do?
Well, how the hell should I know?
Both of you, just calm down.
What's the point of arguing?
So it must be here, a dead person,
I have brought you the police. Yeah!
I'm so glad there are some normal
people living in this town!
Huh, so it seems, Polnareff.
From what I see, I
presume you are travelers.
But with this fog, I'm afraid it's
too dangerous to drive out of town.
I happen to manage a nearby hotel.
I think you'd find it a comfortable
place to spend the night.
Yeah!
A total godsend!
That's what you are!
This is great.
We need a hotel.
Hey, everybody, can we stay there?
Huh?
Can we?
Hmm, all right.
What do you two think about that?
My word, those police
officers are certainly rough.
Yeah, what's with that attitude?
You'd think there were dead bodies
on every street corner around here.
Unbelievable.
Well well my dear guests shall we get
going to the fog is very dense please.
Follow me so you don't
get lost hey old lady
wait up please don't
forget your Luggage we're
leaving now are you
ready anytime we're just
staying for one night So
we don't have much luggage.
Well, well, we have arrived.
This is my hotel.
Here, here, welcoming the party of four.
Come in, come in.
Wow!
I was a little bit worried about what
kind of place that old hag would manage.
But this is a real find.
Yes, so it would seem.
Please, sign right here, Mr. Joestar.
Old lady, just now you used the
name Joestar to refer to him.
Tell me, how do you know that name?
Oh, please, my dear guest.
He was addressed earlier as Mr.
Joestar by him,
that gentleman right over
there. Huh? Who, me? Hmm.
Did I say that or didn't I?
Let me see now.
Wait, well, I... But no, wait.
At the time, I thought I...
Hey, you're the one who called him that.
Just because I'm old,
it doesn't mean you can treat me
like I'm going senile, fanget.
Okay, okay.
Yes, I'm sure I said that, Jotaro.
Now I remember.
Yes, of course, of course.
Didn't I tell you?
because you didn't make yourself clear.
My fault.
My fault, old lady.
Really.
Enya.
A woman.
She's been staying with
us since yesterday.
So, what about her?
No, I just thought it was unusual for
a woman to be traveling by herself.
She's a beautiful lady.
Quite a rare occurrence around here. Yeah?
She's that beautiful a woman?
Mmm, I'd definitely love to
get well acquainted with her.
In your dreams.
Hmm.
I regret to mention that only Mr.
Palnareff's room will be
on the second floor. What?
That's really no problem at all.
By the way, I noticed
that ever since we met,
you've only been using your right hand.
And if you don't mind, I'd like to ask,
Um, is something wrong with your left?
Oh, my left hand.
I burned this hand.
I accidentally spilled hot water on it.
I see.
You really should be
more careful, old lady.
Yes, thank you.
From now on, I will be more careful.
What was that about earlier, Jotaro?
We can't tell who might be an enemy,
so I thought I'd ask a trick question.
Besides, and?
Ever since we arrived in this town,
I've had this feeling that
we're constantly being watched.
Yes, I agree.
A woman from Egypt, a dead body.
Too much of a coincidence.
Oh, room 303.
Hey, this one is mine.
Well, let's talk tomorrow.
Ah, beat!
This bed sure is more
comfortable than that damn truck.
Damn it!
What the hell is up with that
old woman's bandage left hand?
I can't stop thinking about it.
I definitely need a drink.
Oh, yeah. This way.
Hey, that must be the hottie the old
woman in the hotel was talking about.
Barkeep, let's make it two.
A whiskey for me and another
for the lady while you're at it.
The name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
Are you here on a sightseeing
trip with friends?
Or might you be traveling alone, looking
for someone to spend some time with?
My name is...
Enya.
Strange.
It feels like we've
entered a city of the dead.
Who's there?
No one there.
Felt like someone was watching me.
I'm traveling in search of a person.
Well, uh, I'd be happy to
help you in any way I can.
I'm looking for a killer.
A killer?
Whoa!
What are the chances?
I've been out traveling on the
road looking for a killer, too!
Oh, that's weird.
I've been searching for someone
who brutally murdered my son.
My own flesh and blood.
I understand.
I understand how you feel.
Well, somebody, some sick bastard
murdered my younger sister.
I'll help you find that killer, Enya.
What the?
Wait a minute.
That's Whole Horse.
What the hell is he doing here?
What's going on?
What is this guy's problem?
I've got nothing against you.
Something really strange is going on here.
That bartender is no ordinary human.
Why was he trying to kill me?
What is it, Miss Enya?
I didn't finish my story yet, did I?
But you see, I've actually
already found the killer.
You're the man who was dead in
the middle of the street today.
I saw your wounds with my own two eyes.
How is it you can still be alive?
The killer is you, Polareff.
You have been a thorn in
the sight of Lord Dio.
And you are the killer of my son, J. Gile.
Your son?
You gave birth to that murdering bastard?
I take it you've got your
own special kind of stand?
There can only be one stand per person.
But you see, my stand of the mist, the
stand of justice, controls the dead.
Hundreds and thousands are at my disposal
to do as I say, the moment I say it.
See how my beloved clamor for
your attention, Polnareff?
And since they're already
dead, you can't kill them.
Now I get it.
How dare you kill my
precious son, you bastard.
You will pay for it.
Die a slow and painful death. Pull around.